Pray that you drown first.
The Reef is a drama, horror, thriller film directed by Andrew Traucki.
A great white shark hunts the crew of a capsized
sailboat along the Great Barrier Reef.
Luke, played by Damian Walshe-Howling.
Kate, played by Zoe Naylor.
Suzie, played by Adrienne Pickering.
Matt, played by Gyton Grantley.
Warren, played by Kieran Darcy-Smith.
The Reef is a 2010 Australian survival horror film, written, directed and produced by
Andrew Traucki in his second feature film (the first being Black Water).
The film is about a group of friends who capsize while sailing to Indonesia and are
stalked by a great white shark as they try to swim to a nearby island.
A spiritual sequel titled The Reef: Stalked, also written, directed and produced by Traucki, was released in 2022,
and similarly features a cast of characters trying to survive a great white shark stalking them.
The film explores themes of boat, boat accident,
underwater, shark, great white shark.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.